Guide to the Silliman College, Yale University, Student Records of the Classes of 1964-present Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Silliman College, Yale University, student records of the Classes of 1964-present maintained by the dean
1961-2008
RU 257
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
141.25
(219 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Silliman College, Yale University.
Silliman College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-L-1 (YRG 13-L-1), Records of the dean of Silliman College.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Records were transferred from the dean of Silliman College, 1975-2018.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Silliman College, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Silliman College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1964, Circa 1961-1964; Accession 19ND-A-318
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  Related Materials
  Additional withdrawn student files for the class of 1964 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the class of 1964 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
- Student records for the Class of 1965, 1961-1965; Accession 19ND-A-319
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  Additional withdrawn student files for the class of 1965 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the class of 1965 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
- Student records for the Class of 1966, 1962-1966; Accession 19ND-A-320
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  Additional withdrawn student files for the class of 1966 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the class of 1966 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
- Impounded student records for the Classes of 1975-1978, 1971-1978; Accession 1975-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 2, 2054
- Student records for the Classes of 1967-1970, 1963-1970; Accession 1980-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046
  Additional withdrawn student files for the classes of 1967-1970 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the classes of 1967-1970 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
  - Class of 1967
  - Class of 1968
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 1969
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 1970
    - Withdrawn
- Student records, students withdrawn from the Classes of 1964-1975, 1960-1975; Accession 1980-A-027
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051
- Recommendations for students from the Classes of 1964-1976, 1960-1976; Accession 1982-A-037
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  - Class of 1964
  - Class of 1965
  - Class of 1966
  - Class of 1967
  - Class of 1968
  - Class of 1969
  - Class of 1970
  - Class of 1971
  - Class of 1972
  - Class of 1973
  - Class of 1974
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
- Student records for the Class of 1971, 1967-1971; Accession 1983-A-065
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2047
  Withdrawn student files for the class of 1971 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the class of 1971 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
- Student records for the Class of 1972, 1968-1972; Accession 1983-A-066
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2048
  Withdrawn student files for the class of 1972 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the class of 1972 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
- Student records for the Classes of 1973-1974, 1969-1974; Accession 1986-A-093
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
  Additional withdrawn student files for the classes of 1973-1974 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the classes of 1973-1974 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
  - Class of 1973
    - Withdrawals
  - Class of 1974
    - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1975, 1971-1975; Accession 1989-A-034
  Additional withdrawn student files for the class of 1975 are located in RU 257, Accession 1980-A-027. Recommendations for the class of 1975 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
  - Class of 1975, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1976, Accession 1989-A-057
  Recommendations for the class of 1976 are located in RU 257, accession 1982-A-037.
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1977, 1973-1977; Accession 1989-A-078
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  Arrangement
  Material is arranged as student files, letters of recommendations, and withdrawn student files.
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1973-1977
    General
    Folder #120 was assigned to this heading when inventory was created; folder does not exist.
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1978, 1974-1978; Accession 1990-A-125
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  Materials are arranged as student records in alphabetical order, general files, and letters of recommendations in alphabetical order.
  - Withdrawals
  - Commencement 1978 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Freshman 1978 (Box 6, Folder 137)
- Student records for the Class of 1979, 1975-1979; Accession 1990-A-130
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  - WITHDRAWN STUDENTS -Original Class
  - Commencement, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Freshmen, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - RECOMMENDATIONS, 1975-1979
- Student records for the Class of 1980, 1976-1980; Accession 1991-A-090
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  Scope and Contents
  Note: (R) = Recommendation Included
  - Distributional Requirements, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Class of 1980: General, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Commencement 1980, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1981, 1977-1981; Accession 1993-A-010
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1982, 1978-1982; Accession 1993-A-009
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1983, 1979-1983; Accession 1993-A-067
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1984, 1980-1984; Accession 1993-A-068
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1985, 1981-1985; Accession 1994-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1986, 1982-1986; Accession 1994-A-032
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Deceased
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1987, 1983-1987; Accession 1994-A-023
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - Deceased
  - Withdrawn (Box 3)
- Student records for the Classes of 1988-1989, 1984-1989; Accession 1996-A-071
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  * Personal recommendation included in student file
  - Class of 1988
    - Commencement Folder, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Freshmen Folder, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Withdrawals
  - Class of 1989
    - Commencement Folder, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Freshmen Folder, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Tentative
    - Deceased
    - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1990, 1986-1990; Accession 1996-A-078
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Commencement Folder, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Freshmen Folder, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Tentative
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Classes of 1991-1992, 1987-1992; Accession 1998-A-088
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Class of 1991
    - Freshman Folder, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Commencement Folder, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Graduates
    - Tentative
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 1992
    - Graduates
    - Withdrawn, 1988-1992
      Folder #212 was assigned to this heading when inventory was created; folder does not exist.
    - Freshman Folder, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - Commencement Folder, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 241)
- Student records for the Class of 1993, 1989-1993; Accession 2001-A-087
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1994, 1990-1994; Accession 2001-A-088
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1995, 1991-1995; Accession 2002-A-184
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  RU 257, Accession 2002-A-185 (Class of 1996) also includes files pertaining to commencement, faculty advisors and fresman advisors for the class of 1995.
  - * Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1996, 1991-1996; Accession 2002-A-185
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  Accession also includes files pertaining to commencement, faculty advisors and fresman advisors for the classes of 1995 and 1996.
  An asterix (*) indicates that a personal recommendation is included in student file.
  - Withdrawn
  - Class of 1995 Commencement files (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Class of 1995 Freshman counselors, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Class of 1995 Freshman faculty advisors, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Class of 1996 Commencement (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Class of 1996 Freshman counselors, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Class of 1996 Freshman faculty advisors, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 120)
- Student records for the Class of 1997, 1993-1997; Accession 2007-A-088
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1998, 1994-1998; Accession 2008-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Withdrawals
  - Freshman Counselors, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Commencement, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 128 - 129)
- Student records for the Classes of 2001-2006, 1997-2006; Accession 2010-A-077
  Restricted 75 years from date of graduation.
  - Class of 2001
    Restricted until July 2076.
  - Class of 2002
    Restricted until July 2077.
    - Withdrawals
  - Class of 2003
    Restricted until July 2078.
    - Withdrawals
  - Class of 2004
    Restricted until July 2079.
    - Ex Class of 2004
  - Class of 2005
    Restricted until July 2080.
    - Ex Class of 2005
  - Class of 2006
    Restricted until July 2081.
    - Ex Class of 2006
- Student records for the Classes of 1999, 2000 and 2007, 1987-2007; Accession 2011-A-039
  - Class of 1999
    - Withdrawals
  - Class of 2000
    Restricted until July 2075.
    - Withdrawals
  - Class of 2007
    Restricted until January 1, 2083.
- Student records for the Class of 2008, 2004-2008; Accession 2019-A-0011
  Restricted until 2084 as established by Yale Corporation regulations http://web.library.yale.edu/mssa/collections/research-use-of-yale-university-archives.
  - Adams, Bryce, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agawu, Atu, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ahearn, Rachel, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Andrews, Brett, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arkow, Michelle, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bai, Xiao (Harrison), 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bandyopadhyay, Sudipta, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Barth, Adam J., 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 7a)
  - Beck, Milton, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bernard, Lisa, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bialecki, Jessica, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bibler, Bryan, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biesecker, Emily, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bordoni, Matthew, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bottini, Alexander, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Brockman, Stephanie, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Callsen, Gilman, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Campbell, Kristen, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Carden, Stephen, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cavoulacos, Alexandra, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Champion, Jessica, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chang, Jack, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cheng, Lulu, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chien, Stephen, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - China, George, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Chiueh, Shenghao, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - DeGraff, Bassel, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 25a)
  - Denenberg, Andrew, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - DeTurck, Gary, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Diaz, Gabriel, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dikas, Kenneth, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Drapala, Michael, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Elkins, Benjamin, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Enriquez, Angel, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Errico, John, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Evans, Chloe Marie, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Green, Rory A., 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 34a)
  - Gresham, Louis, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Grove, Marian, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Guy, Shannon, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Hamilton, Thomas, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Hayase, Justin, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Higginbotham, Lenora, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Holdren, Sarah, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Hollander, Brandt, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Holmes, Caleb, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Holmes, Nicholas, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Huang, Mengmeng, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Hutchinson, Christa Michelle, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Jack-Scott, Emily, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Johnson, Anna, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Johnson, Candace, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Johnston, Adam, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Kadesch, Alison, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Kaufman, Lisbeth, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Keane, Catherine, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Kerns, Caroline, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Kimball, Jessica, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kraseski, Courtney, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Krause, Andrew, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Levine, Mimi, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lin, Diana, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Liquido, Francisco, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - London, George, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lupica, Charles, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Magliocco, Matthew, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Malagon, Carolina, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Marker, David, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - McDermott, Noel, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Meredith, Adam, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Morin, Esteban, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Moy, Ryan, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Nagler, Daniel, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Nicewicz, Peter, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - O'Bryant, E. Maurice, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Palmieri, Stafford, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Park, Jennifer, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Peterson, Jason, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Preston, Katrina, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Raghavan, Lavanya, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Rawson, David, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Rittelmeyer, Helen, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Rodriguez, Cassandra, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Rothmeier, Alexander, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Rosenblum, Andrew Michael, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Rowe, Rachel, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Saltzman, Rachel Ward, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Sanchez, Seve, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Schmidt, Kathryn, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Showole, Olufunmilayo, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Soltoff, Cain, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - St. Victor, Elizabeth, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Stephen, Clarence, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Stockton, Vanessa, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Sun, Jeffrey, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Swaba, Anatasha Marie Mahiki, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Sweren, Joshua, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Takabvirwa, Kathryn, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Takahashi, Mari-e, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Tan, Steven, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Taylor, Kiersten, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Taylor, Lauren, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Thais, Roberto, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Theofilos, Tyler, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Toubolets, Daniel, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tuna, Cari, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Varghese, Ravi, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vespe, Michael, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - White, Samuel, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Wild, Aaron, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Windmuller, Kristen, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wofsey, Michelle, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Xu, Hang, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Zackheim, Emmett, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Zagha, David, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Zamora, Elizabeth, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Zhang, TaoTao, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)